#### **Personal Information**

Name Muhammad Afiq Farhan Bin Mohd Anuar

Address No.63 Lorong Sungai Puluh 5E

Taman Cempaka Sari 3

42100 Klang, Selangor Darul Ehsan

**E-mail** farhan\_afiq91@yahoo.com

**Phone** 016-6864592



### **Career Objective**

As Accountancy graduate with good academic standing applying for a General Accounting position where I can use my knowledge and experience to ensure the delivery of all financial and accounting activities related to accounts payable, accounts receivables and general accounting.

#### **Education**

University

Institution University Selangor (UNISEL)
Course Bachelor of Accounting (Honours)

Concentration Accounting Year 2013-2015 CGPA 2.98

University

Institution University Selangor (UNISEL)
Level Bachelor of Accounting (Honours)

Major Accounting
Concentration Finance
Year 2009-2012
CGPA 2.49

# **Work Experiences**

## **Account Analyst**

Mahzan Sulaiman Plt

01 March 2016 - Current

Account Department

- Prepare Full Set of Account for a few company
- Do the monthly submission for GST
- Prepare management accounts slide
- Do the audit for Dormant company
- Prepare the submission Form E for company

### **Internship** (Trainee)

Usaha Korporat Tax Services Sdn Bhd

**January 2015 – July 2015** 

- Prepare Full Set of Account for a few company
- Do the audit for Dormant company
- Prepare the submission Form E for company

#### **Administrative**

Fathani Construction

**January 2012 – June 2012** 

- Prepare invoices for the client
- Do the progress claim for the work done

#### **Extra-curricular activities**

2012	$6^{\text{th}}$ SEMESTER EDUCATION VISIT TO JABATAN AKAUNTAN NEGARA
2012	1st SEMESTER MIA CARE AWARENESS TALK
2013	5 <sup>th</sup> SEMESTER EDUCATION VISIT TO PHN INDUSTRY SDN BHD
2014	6th SEMESTER SEMINAR IN AUDITING & ACCOUNTING 2014
2014	6 <sup>th</sup> SEMESTER TALK SHOW PERSONAL MONEY MANAGEMENT
2014	6th SEMESTER EXPLORACE STREET FINANCE FEST 2014
2014	6 <sup>th</sup> SEMESTER CERAMAH PERDANA GST 17 APRIL2014
2015	8th SEMESTER FORUM PELABURAN DALAM ISLAM

# Language and Skills

Language ProficiencyWrittenSpokenEnglishModerateModerateBahasa MalaysiaExcellentExcellent

Computer Software LiteracyLevelUBS Accounting SystemModerateQuickBooks Pro Accounting SystemAdvanceMicrosoft Office: Word, Power Point, Excel, AccessAdvanceMYOB Accounting SystemAdvance

### References

Name : Mr.Zaini Azizi Bin Azizol

Relationship : Manager Analyst at Mahzan Sulaim Plt

Telephone : 014-500 1029

Email : zainiazizi2013@gmail.com

Name : Miss Chan Wai Ling

Relationship : Manager at Usaha Korporat Tax Services Sdn Bhd

Telephone : 03-7983 3330

Name : Mr.Mohd Anuar Bin Daud

Relationship : Manager at Fathani Construction

Telephone : 016-3314025